Inventory of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos Collection AD.RG.009.1.2.2
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos
Fall 2013 - Spring 2020
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
AD.RG.009.1.2.2
84.14 Gigabytes
The NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos collection is a collection of digital images, as well as some music and video files, from a variety of student and campus events during Academic Years 2014 - 2020.
Biographical / Historical
Programs of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life, part of the Division of Student Affairs (previously Campus Life), include a variety of events and activities arranged to cultivate engagement and inclusivity across the NYUAD campus. The Manager of Campus Facilities is part of a team of staff that advises on and arranges space and services to ensure events are successful. This includes photography and audiovisual arrangements.
Content Description
The NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos collection is a collection of digital images, as well as some music and video files, from a variety of student and campus events during Academic Years 2014 - 2020. The collection was maintained, organized and transferred to the University Archives by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Dowdall also transferred files he inherited from his predecessor, Alex Heald.
Events that are documented range from student field trips, to campus festivals, to other campus events such as Autism Awareness Week, Latino Night, Marhaba, Staff Appreciation Day, and Defend the Nest, among others.
A small file of administrative and program records from the desk of the Student Life Coordinator, Fall 2013-Spring 2015, were also transferred as part of this collection.
Arrangement
The collection has been minimally processed and its original arrangement by academic year has been retained.
Conditions Governing Access
This digital collection is accessible to members of the NYU Abu Dhabi community and the NYU Global Network. It is available for viewing in the Archives and Special Collections reading room, or remotely by request.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual material is born-digital and available for viewing on a computer workstation in the Archives and Special Collections Reading Room, facilitated by ASC staff.
- Student Life Event Coordinator, Fall 2013 - Spring 2015; 34.7 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  Mixed program and administrative files. Includes these subfolders:
  Brochure, Budget, FileRelease, Flavors of Abu Dhabi, Forms, Linajma, Ma_a Salama, Ma_a Salama 2015, Marhaba 2013, Marhaba 2014, Newsletter, NYUAD Brand Pack, Saadiyat, Student Info.
- AY13-14 (Alex Heald), Fall 2013 - Spring 2014; 429.7 Megabytes
  Images and documents maintained by the Manager of Student Life Facilities, Alex Heald, from the period 2013-2014. Includes the following subfolders:
  Ajman Kashtah, AustraliaNZ, Autism Event, Breakthrough, Class of 2014, Dubai Kashtah, Fujairah Camping, GIN 2014, HULT, Latino Night, Linajma, Mangroves, National Day, Old Photos, Random, Sama Cup Outreach, Saudi VIP, Taste From Home Malaysian, and USA Canada Night.
  - Ajman Kashtah, 136 Megabytes
  - AustraliaNZ, 51.2 Megabytes
- AY14-15 (Alex Heald), Fall 2014 - Spring 2015; 1.67 Gigabytes
  Includes images from a variety of events and field trips, maintained by Student Life Facilities Manager Alex Heald. Includes the following subfolders:
  Al Wathba Camel Races, As One Screening, Autism Awareness Lunch, Class of 2015 Photos, Community Outreach Fair, Debate, Della Mae Bluegrass, Diplomacy in Action, Dubomedy March 2015, East Asia Night, Falcon_s Flood, Flavors - Russian Kitchen, FYD Service Weekend, Terry Fox Run.
- AY14-15 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2014 - Spring 2015; 483.6 Megabytes
  Images and audio files from academic year 2014-2015, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Includes the following subfolders:
  AY15 Dubomedy March 2015, AY15 Latino Night 2015, AY15 National Day 43 Event, AY15 Saadiyat After Hours Event Calender.
- AY15-16 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2015 - Spring 2016; 3.83 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2015-2016, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Includes these subfolders:
  AY16 Arab Culture Night, AY16 Autism Awareness Walk, Abu Dhabi TV Footage - Autism Awareness Community Walk.mp4,, AY16 Latino Night,, AY16 National Day 44, AY16 Park Hyatt Residence Images, AY16 PSA Mock Wedding, AY16 Spring Fest March 2016, AY16 Tashan Sri Lankan New Year.
- AY16-17 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2016 - Spring 2017; 14.85 Gigabytes
  Images from academic year 2016-2017, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Includes these subfolders:
  AY17 Africa Carribean Night April 2017, AY17 Asia Pacific Night November 2016, AY17 DJs in D1 March 2017, AY17 Dubai Kastag and Etihad Museum Images 2017, AY17 Dubomody August 2017, AY17 Halloween 2016 NYUAD, AY17 Halloween Community NYUAD 2016, AY17 Kastag Dubai February 2017, AY17 Latino Night 2017, AY17 Marhaba 17 D1 Images, AY17 Marhaba Captains and Leaders Karaoke Night August 26, AY17 Marhaba Heritage Village, AY17 Marhaba Speed Meeting, AY17 Marhaba Variety Show 22 August, AY17 Mock Wedding, AY17 National Day 45 Images 2016, AY17 Qhapag Nan February 2017, AY17 So You Think You Cant Dance February 2017, AY17 Staff Appreciation Day October 2016, AY17 Student Ball April 2017, AY17 Student Marhaba Dance Park Hyatt August 24, AY17 Sufaraa BBQ February 2017, AY17 Ultra Violet Live November 2016.
- AY17-18 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2017 - Spring 2018; 27.14 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2017-2018, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Includes these subfolders:
  Africa Carribean Night April 2017, AY 18 Attitide Dance SIG Just Dance September 2017, AY18 Awkward Dance Competition November 2017, AY18 DJ Showcase October 2017, AY18 Enrico Santcatterina Jam session, AY18 First and Second Class Event Nov 2017, AY18 Halloween Karaoke 2017 D1, AY18 Halloween NYUAD 2017, AY18 Marhaba Student Gov Dance, AY18 Open Mic 3 2018, AY18 Pakistan Mock Wedding April 2018, AY18 Pink Fitness Games Event October 2017, AY18 Real AD Show September 2017, AY18 Staff Appreciation Day 1_ 8 November 2017, AY18 Volunteer Appreciation 11 December 2017.
- AY18-19 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2018 - Spring 2019; 7.2 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2018-2019, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Includes these subfolders:
  AY 19 Marhaba Images for Victor Lindsay, AY19 Arab Culture Club February 2019, AY19 Holi March 2019, AY19 Latino Night April 2019, AY19 Staff Appreciation Day Folder.
- AY19-20 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2019 - Spring 2020; 28.5 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2019-2020, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Includes these subfolders:
  AY20 ADNH Top Chef September 2019, AY20 Afro Fest November 2019, AY20 BK Gulf Event 21 January 2020, AY20 Defeat the Deans November 2019, AY20 Defend the Nest November 2019, AY20 Diwali November 2019, AY20 Falcon Feast September 2019, AY20 Go Green Group Photos 2020, AY20 GO Green Week February 2020, AY20 Hazel and Jay December 2019, AY20 Jackie Soul Food February 2020, AY20 John Sexton Talk October 2019, AY20 Marhaba Carnival 2019, AY20 Marhaba Welcome Dance August 2019, AY20 MSF November 2019, AY20 National Day 2019, AY20 Nurdle Hunt Images, AY20 Prince Hamilton December 2019, AY20 Staff Appreciation Day 1 October 2019, AY20 Student Life Open House 16 September 2019, AY20 Swimming Pool, AY20 UAE Majlis SIG September 2019.